<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Arthur Wu</title>
    <link>https://example.org/projects/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Arthur Wu</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-GB</language>
      <atom:link href="https://example.org/projects/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>HooRides</title>
      <link>https://example.org/projects/hoorides/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/projects/hoorides/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;HooRides is a carpooling app that was developed with the University of Virginia community in mind. Built with React Native and Firebase, HooRides is a cross-platform application that facilitates rides for UVA students and faculty to and from Charlottesville. So far, 1000+ km of rides have been scheduled using HooRides.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>SupportBot</title>
      <link>https://example.org/projects/supportbot/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/projects/supportbot/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I spearheaded the development of a customer support chatbot for Babylon Micro-Farms with React.js and the OpenAI Assistants API. I led a team of 4 software engineers using Agile project management methodology, achieving project competion ahead of schedule and delivering a polished web application to Babylon Micro-Farms which improved the efficiency of their account management and customer support teams. Later, I presented the chatbot application to the Babylon Micro-Farms CTO and Head of Data Science, fostering a continued shift in their customer support strategy.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>theCourseForum</title>
      <link>https://example.org/projects/install/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      <guid>https://example.org/projects/install/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;I&amp;rsquo;m part of a team of 20+ engineers at a University of Virginia-funded nonprofit which develops an academic planning web application called theCourseForum. I helped revamp the user authentication page by implementing responsive authentication to expedite login, benefitting 41,000+ users with significant time savings. I also worked with CI tools such as GitHub Actions to ensure successful application deployment for over 41,000 users alongside an actively growing codebase.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
